gadgetunlocker.com 2016-01-25

# Privacy Policy - Gadget Unlocker

## Privacy Policy

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally identifiable information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

**On our site we collect the following:**

Email address

**Information is collected from you when you:**

**The information collected from you is used in the following ways:**

To administer contests, promotions, or a survey or other site feature

**How do we protect visitor information?**

We use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.

We do not use an SSL certificate

**•**  We only provide articles and information, and we never ask for personal or private information

**Do we use ‘cookies’?**

**We use cookies to:**

**•**  Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart,

It won’t affect the users experience

**Third Party Disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer Personally Identifiable Information.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Google**

We have not enable Google Adwords on our site but we may do so on the future.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act**

**According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:**

Users can visit our site anonymously

Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.

Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’, and can be easily be found on the page specified above.

Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:

**•**  On our Privacy Policy Page

Users are able to change their personal information:

**•**  By logging in to their account

**How does our site handle do not track signals?**

We honor them and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

**Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?**

We do not allow

**COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**

We do not specifically market to children under 13

**Fair Information Practices**

**In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:**

We will notify the users via email

**•**  Within 1 business day

We agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors

**Contact Information**

Bangalore

India

Bangalore

Karnataka

560102

gadgetunlocker@gmail.com

1
